Daniel E Lake

danlake2012@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://dan-lakes-portfolio-page.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/dan-lake-media/

15 Crestview Dr Elizabethtown, PA 17022 717-454-8385

Summary Statement

Ongoing training with Html, Css, and JS from W3schools keeps me up to date with the latest changes. Thorough knowledge of hardware from building computers as a hobby. Website construction and Youtube media experience have given me great hands-on knowledge of multiple platforms.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, SASS, PYTHON, TAILWIND, SANITY

Operating Systems: Windows, Mac OS, Linux

Applications: Microsoft Office; Google Docs; Compilers such as Spyder, VS Code, Atom, Google ads, WordPress

Education

Central Penn College - Information Technology - Associates Degree - Application Development

Anticipated Graduation September 2022

Major GPA: 3.0

Work Experience

Lead Install Trainer/Multi-Media Associate, **Home Climates Inc**, Elizabethtown, PA, August 2021– Present Providing home comfort for residential customers by means of air conditioning, heating and plumbing.

- Created Multiple materials, parts, and tool lists for the retro install dept with Excel.
- Introduced videos of job-related tasks for future employees and for special events.
- Currently on safety committee making worksites safer for employees.
- Responsible for training 6 installers and trainees on how to install and troubleshoot residential heating and cooling systems.

Hvac Service Technician, Leo Kob Inc, Elizabethtown, PA, April 2020 – August 2021

Commercial and residential contractor of heating and cooling products

- Residential service and installation technician.
- Commercial service technician responsible for after-hours on-call service.
- Completed hundreds of preventative maintenance plans.

Owner, Lake's Hvac Service LLC, Elizabethtown, PA, November 2017- April 2020

Home comfort by means of heating, cooling and plumbing products.

- Created own business by providing residential heating and cooling services.
- Installed new equipment to provide home comfort.
- Designed own website with WordPress and multi-media pages along with advertising on Google Adwords.
- Used Quickbooks for accounting and point of sale gateway.

Military Experience And Training

Squad Leader/Maintenance Sergeant, United States Army, Ft. Indiantown Gap, PA, April 1992 - July 2017 Security Force of our great nation.

- Led 11 men and women in their 20s in a daily routine to become better physically, mentally, and in a team environment.
- As a maintenance Sergeant, I was responsible for the services and repairs of military vehicles and tools.
- Self-development was a priority of mine and will always be one.

Extracurricular Activities

- Created my own Youtube Channel in 2020 creating woodworking and website creation videos.
- https://www.youtube.com/c/AmericanWoodsmith
- https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC9FmWMMHgm6yLEjxef9dLsQ